KRISH KHULLAR

UNIVERSITY STUDENT

CONTACT

+1 (778) 997-7508

krishkhullar.20@gmail.com

in LinkedIn

My Portfolio

GitHub

EDUCATION

Okanagan, Canada University of British Columbia

2023 - present

BSc, Major in Computer Science, 2nd Year Academic achievement: Dean's List (1st Yr)

Hamala, Bahrain British School Of Bahrain

2017 - 2023

LANGUAGES & INTERESTS



English IELTS 8.5 French B1 cert. **Hindi** Native



Puzzles, Competitive, Art, photography, Games, Scuba Diving, Badminton, UX/UI designing

CERTIFICATIONS

Coursera React Basic | Meta

Coursera
Google UX design course | Google

PIRPLE Purple Tutor
C++ HTML5, CSS3 & JS

PROFILE

As a dedicated Computer Science student with a strong passion for problem-solving and innovation, I specialize in web development, coding, and UI/UX design. My project experience includes developing web applications, creating algorithms for competitive programming, and designing user-friendly interfaces.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Work Experience

Kumon Kelowna (2024) | Provided personalized instruction in math and reading
to students of varying ages and skill levels and assisted in administrative tasks,
including grading assignments and maintaining student records.

Leadership Experiences

- Hello India (2021) | Mentored an individual to improve English proficiency by 35% through structured activities and guided conversations.
- Code Bozu Cornell University (2021) | Led a team of 5 to solve over 10 programming problems and develop a web scraper, placing in the top 20% internationally.
- Engineering Forum (2022 2023) | Conducted research on environmental sustainability, organizing members to investigate and present on various science fields.
- Computer Science Club (2022-2023) | Grew membership from 3 to 22 students, creating a review forum for exam preparation and exploring advanced topics.

Volunteering Experiences

- The People (2021) | Managed and cataloged a database of over 100 books, enhancing accessibility and familiarity with DBMS systems.
- Royal Hospital for Women and Children (2022) | Shadowed staff across 15 departments, gaining insights into hospital management systems and operations.
- ECO-HUB (2021-2022) | Collaborated on creating a pocket forest, revitalizing local land, and representing the organization at 4 promotional events.

Skill set

Technical Skills

Python · C++ · Java · JavaScript · HTML5 & CSS3 (including Bootstrap and Tailwind frameworks) · ReactJS · UI/UX Design

Critical Skills

Algorithm Design · Problem Solving · Project Leadership · Collaboration · Adaptability · Networking · Mentorship · Work drive · Competitive Programming · Time Management · Initiative · Creativity